
Welcome to Gradle 8.11.1!

Here are the highlights of this release:
 - Parallel load and store for Configuration Cache
 - Java compilation errors at the end of the build output
 - Consolidated report for warnings and deprecations

For more details see https://docs.gradle.org/8.11.1/release-notes.html

Starting a Gradle Daemon, 1 incompatible Daemon could not be reused, use --status for details
[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/Users/User/AndroidStudioProjects/Spirale/Spirala1/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 9.0.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/8.11.1/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
